<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.8.7">
  <compounddef id="DeviceAliasParser" kind="page">
    <compoundname>DeviceAliasParser</compoundname>
    <title>Cisco &quot;show device-alias database&quot;</title>
    <detaileddescription>
<para>The <ref refid="classorg_1_1smallfoot_1_1parser_1_1zone_1_1DeviceAliasParser" kindref="compound">DeviceAliasParser</ref> parses the output of a Cisco SAN switch with the &quot;show device-alias database&quot; command</para><para>As always, this parser is more successful when the content is treated like binary: don&apos;t edit it. In particular, the use of a putty log to capture output while querying the switch leads to parser exceptions because the interactive "you have connected to blah blah system version 1.2.3, the weather is fabulous and I have 42 pages of boilerplate to spit out before you enter the command for aliases... hit enter to continue... have some backspaces..." is included. As are the backspaces.</para><para>When collecting aliases using an ssh command, it&apos;s better to execute that command noninteractively:</para><para>In UNIX, Linux, Ubuntu, OSX, or the 6000 other licensees of the USL codebase: <verbatim>ssh username@switch44.example.com &quot;show device-alias database&quot; &gt; switch44.dad
</verbatim></para><para>In windows, using the <ulink url="http://www.chiark.greenend.org.uk/~sgtatham/putty/download.html">putty</ulink> tools: <verbatim>plink.exe -l username -pw p4ssw0rd switch44.example.com &quot;show device-alias database&quot; &gt; switch44.dad
</verbatim></para><para>This leads to a better chance to parse 100% of the output with more accuracy, but I guess following this recommendation is up to the user, and to the engineer suggesting how he or she should collect the text for parsing.</para><para><verbatim>The copyrights to certain works contained in this software are
owned by other third parties and used and distributed under
license. Certain components of this software are licensed under
the GNU General Public License (GPL) version 2.0 or the GNU
Lesser General Public License (LGPL) Version 2.1. A copy of each
such license is available at
http://www.opensource.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.php and
http://www.opensource.org/licenses/lgpl-2.1.php
switch44a# show device-alias database
device-alias name server44_hba0 pwwn 10:00:00:00:c9:12:34:56
device-alias name server44_hba1 pwwn 10:00:00:00:c9:12:34:57
device-alias name oracle10_hba0 pwwn 21:00:00:24:ff:12:34:56
device-alias name oracle10_hba1 pwwn 22:00:00:24:ff:12:34:56
device-alias name vmax-18641-fa06a0 pwwn 50:00:09:72:01:23:45:54
device-alias name vmax-18641-fa07a0 pwwn 50:00:09:72:01:23:45:58 </verbatim></para><para>with the following result of WWPN/alias pairs: <verbatim>10000000c9123456,&quot;server44_hba0&quot;
10000000c9123457,&quot;server44_hba1&quot;
21000024ff123456,&quot;oracle10_hba0&quot;
22000024ff123456,&quot;oracle10_hba1&quot;
5000097201234554,&quot;vmax-18641-fa06a0&quot;
5000097201234558,&quot;vmax-18641-fa07a0&quot; </verbatim> </para>    </detaileddescription>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
