<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.8.7">
  <compounddef id="jvmopt" kind="page">
    <compoundname>jvmopt</compoundname>
    <title>JVM Options</title>
    <detaileddescription>
<para><variablelist>
<varlistentry><term><anchor id="jvmopt_1_jvmopt000001"/>Global <ref refid="classorg_1_1smallfoot_1_1parser_1_1bnapsql_1_1BNAPURLConnection_1a0924d1107a459be632532ef34324494e" kindref="member">BNAPURLConnection.getInputStream</ref>  ()</term></varlistentry>
<listitem><para><bold>debug.carleton</bold>: For testing and additional info, -Ddebug.carleton causes the &quot;old&quot; query to be swapped with a pull from hba_target_info  </para></listitem>
<varlistentry><term><anchor id="jvmopt_1_jvmopt000003"/>Global <ref refid="classorg_1_1smallfoot_1_1parser_1_1zone_1_1NicknameParser_1ac7c2594b796ab3c7107f9a55b4fc8488" kindref="member">NicknameParser.NicknameParser</ref>  (java.util.Properties properties)</term></varlistentry>
<listitem><para><bold>wwn</bold> (values: numbers, 0-32767) can be used to indicate that the WWPN for a WWPN/Alias pair is not the default column #0 (first column)</para><para><programlisting><codeline><highlight class="normal">java<sp/>-Dwwn=4<sp/>-jar<sp/>fcparser.jar<sp/>-N<sp/>...<sp/><sp/></highlight></codeline>
</programlisting> It is preferred that a more local non-global setting be used, by appending to the URL: <programlisting><codeline><highlight class="normal">java<sp/>-jar<sp/>fcparser.jar<sp/>-N<sp/></highlight><highlight class="stringliteral">&quot;cisco.txt;wwn=4&quot;</highlight><highlight class="normal"><sp/>...<sp/><sp/></highlight></codeline>
</programlisting>  </para></listitem>
<varlistentry><term><anchor id="jvmopt_1_jvmopt000007"/>Global <ref refid="classorg_1_1smallfoot_1_1parser_1_1ssh_1_1SSHURLConnection_1aa4711ecd1154e59ce7dabf904ed49c16" kindref="member">SSHURLConnection._connect</ref>  ()</term></varlistentry>
<listitem><para><bold>debug.dumpSSHPreConnect</bold> (values: true, false) can be used to dump out the User/Pass Authentication info before the client connects to the remote server. Note that this can cause plaintext revelation of private credential info</para><para><programlisting><codeline><highlight class="normal">java<sp/>-Ddebug.dumpSSHPreConnect=</highlight><highlight class="keyword">true</highlight><highlight class="normal"><sp/>-jar<sp/>fcparser.jar<sp/>-N<sp/>...<sp/><sp/></highlight></codeline>
</programlisting> </para><para><bold>debug.dumpSSHAuthInfo</bold> (values: true, false) can be used to dump out the User/Pass Authentication info before the client connects to the remote server. Note that this can cause plaintext revelation of private credential info</para><para><programlisting><codeline><highlight class="normal">java<sp/>-Ddebug.dumpSSHAuthInfo=</highlight><highlight class="keyword">true</highlight><highlight class="normal"><sp/>-jar<sp/>fcparser.jar<sp/>-N<sp/>...<sp/><sp/></highlight></codeline>
</programlisting>  </para></listitem>
<varlistentry><term><anchor id="jvmopt_1_jvmopt000012"/>Class <ref refid="classorg_1_1smallfoot_1_1parser_1_1zone_1_1ZoneParserI" kindref="compound">ZoneParserI</ref>  </term></varlistentry>
<listitem><para><bold>debug.verboseTokenizer</bold> (values: true, Alias4Parser, AliShowZoneParser, BNAZoneParser, DeviceAliasParser, NicknameParser, ShowZoneParser, VW4InvalidAddedParser) can be set to either &quot;true&quot;, or to the name of a specific parser (ie ShowZoneParser) to cause the parser&apos;s tokenizing and returned tokens to be displayed. Of note: this will show when the parser sees a value it doesn&apos;t like, such as an improper symbol, word, or key term. This can be helpful in diagnosing why the parser gave up and/or the calling process didn&apos;t feel this parser&apos;s results were worth keeping or using. Alias4Parser and NicknameParser are not LALR-based but do give some indications by this option.</para><para><programlisting><codeline><highlight class="normal">java<sp/>-Ddebug.verboseTokenizer=NicknameParser<sp/>-jar<sp/>fcparser.jar<sp/>-N<sp/>...<sp/></highlight></codeline>
</programlisting></para><para><bold>debug.dumpAliases</bold> (values: true, Alias4Parser, AliShowZoneParser, BNAZoneParser, DeviceAliasParser, NicknameParser, ShowZoneParser, VW4InvalidAddedParser) can be used to tell most parsers to dump out their results for diagnostics. Setting it to &quot;true&quot; would cause all to dump their results; setting to the name of a Parser (ie ShowZoneParser, VW4InvalidAddedParser, NicknameParser) would cause that individual parser to show its results. These names are the same names listed at the end of a parse attempt for convenience/aide-memoire.</para><para><programlisting><codeline><highlight class="normal">java<sp/>-Ddebug.dumpAliases=AliShowZoneParser<sp/>-jar<sp/>fcparser.jar<sp/>-N<sp/>...<sp/><sp/></highlight></codeline>
</programlisting></para><para><bold>debug.dumpItems</bold> (values: Aliases, reservedAliases) can be used to tell most parsers to dump out additional results directly for diagnostics. For example, VW4InvalidAddedParser can track post-remove aliases in the mapping &quot;reservedAliases&quot;</para><para><programlisting><codeline><highlight class="normal">java<sp/>-Ddebug.dumpItems=reservedAliases<sp/>-jar<sp/>fcparser.jar<sp/>-N<sp/>...<sp/><sp/></highlight></codeline>
</programlisting></para><para><bold>debug.verboseAddAlias</bold>: (values: true, Alias4Parser, AliShowZoneParser, BNAZoneParser, DeviceAliasParser, ShowZoneParser, VW4InvalidAddedParser) Although not much use without looking inside the code, setting this value allows you to see when the parser is storing a new alias block/set internally for retrieval by the calling function. It might help you to see where the incorrect data is coming from.</para><para><bold>debug.verboseAddZone</bold>: (values: true, Alias4Parser, AliShowZoneParser, BNAZoneParser, DeviceAliasParser, ShowZoneParser, VW4InvalidAddedParser) Although not much use without looking inside the code, setting this value allows you to see when the parser is storing a new zone block internally for retrieval by the calling function. It might help you to see where the incorrect data is coming from.</para><para><bold>debug.verboseAppendZone</bold>: (values: true, Alias4Parser, AliShowZoneParser, BNAZoneParser, DeviceAliasParser, ShowZoneParser, VW4InvalidAddedParser) Although not much use without looking inside the code, setting this value allows you to see when the parser is adding data to an existing zone value internally for retrieval by the calling function. It might help you to see where the incorrect data is coming from.</para><para><bold>debug.yystate</bold>: (values: true, AliShowZoneParser, BNAZoneParser, DeviceAliasParser, ShowZoneParser, VW4InvalidAddedParser) Although not much use without looking inside the code, setting this value allows you to see the debug information from inside the LALR state machine itself. This might give some insight as to why some parse attempts are failing, or how the state-machine needs to be extended to accommodate more situations. </para></listitem>
</variablelist>
</para>    </detaileddescription>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
